hey spring fans today we're gonna go
嘿，今天的春季歌迷，我们要去
ahead and take a look at some of the
向前看一些
low-level interfaces in the spring
春季的低层接口
framework itself that allow you to write
框架本身，使您可以编写
code that is more aware of the
更了解
application context in container why you
容器中的应用程序上下文为什么
would want to do this is sort of a
想做到这一点有点
varied by case-by-case of course but
视情况而定，但
suffice it to say you shouldn't have to
足以说明您不必
do this very often so I just want to
经常这样做，所以我只想
explain some of what these things are
解释一些这些东西是什么
what some of these opportunities are and
这些机会是什么？
I want to show you things you may have
我想告诉你你可能拥有的东西
seen but didn't quite understand because
看过但不太了解，因为
it's not very common to use some of
使用一些不常见
these things in the java configuration
这些东西在java配置中
esque a sort of world of spring boudin
仿佛春天布丁的世界
and spring 3 data or later but if you've
和春季3数据或更高版本，但如果您已经
got old code you may have seen these
有旧代码，您可能已经看到这些
things around so this might be a useful
周围的事情，所以这可能是有用的
primer on some of those things and maybe
读一些其中的东西，也许
you'll even learn something new as well
您甚至还会学到一些新东西
so go ahead we're gonna go ahead and
所以继续前进，我们将继续前进，
create a new a new project here called
在这里创建一个新的新项目
spring where I'm not gonna bring in
我不会带进来的春天
anything specific I don't need anything
任何具体的我什么都不需要
specific I'm just gonna use spring
具体我只是要用弹簧
framework itself the application context
框架本身的应用程序上下文
and all that gets set up for me by the
而所有的一切都由我为
spring boot starter default depends and
Spring Boot Starter默认取决于
it gets added by by choosing nothing on
通过不选择任何东西来添加它
the spring initializer so I'll start
春天的初始值设定项，让我开始
this up and what we're gonna talk about
这个，我们要谈论的是
today are we're gonna talk about several
今天我们要谈几个
different things the first thing we're
不同的东西我们第一件事
gonna look at is how to manage the
要看的是如何管理
lifecycle of an object right so again
对象的生命周期正确
that's great let's go ahead and create a
太好了，让我们继续创建一个
couple of classes here right two objects
这里有两个类，两个对象
that work with each other one of the
彼此合作的
both the other is a class foo class bar
对方都是一个foo类的类吧
and they're related to each other right
他们彼此相关
and so in theory one could have a
因此从理论上讲，
dependency on the other create a
对另一个的依赖
constructor now I have an object here
构造函数现在我在这里有一个对象
and I can do the initialization of you
我可以对你进行初始化
know of the foo entirely in the
完全了解foo
constructor right this is a good place
构造函数对，这是个好地方
to put that logic because in so far I've
说出逻辑，因为到目前为止
got all in in that I've got all of my
拥有全部，因为我拥有全部
collaborating objects - required to set
协作对象-需要设置
up subject in a valid state provided in
在有效状态下提供
the constructor
构造函数
I'm good to go but sometimes I may have
我很好，但是有时候我可能有
setters I may have other things that are
二传手我可能还有其他事情
provided later on so maybe I don't get
以后提供，所以也许我不明白
them all in the constructor maybe I have
他们都在构造函数中，也许我有
a initialization that happens via a
初始化通过
setter here right until will say cetera
在这里的二传手，直到会说cetera
voila now I need some call back some
瞧，我现在需要一些回电
hook after both the constructor and the
在构造函数和
setters have run and for this we're
二传手已经跑了，为此，我们
going to look at some of we can look at
要看一些我们可以看的
the spring initializing being in two
春天初始化在两个
right so initializing beam is a an
对，所以初始化光束是一个
interface that's been in spring since
自春季以来的界面
day one since one natto at least and
从纳 bean 开始的第一天，至少
some time before that as well and here
在此之前还有一段时间
we have an ideal opportunity to do kind
我们有一个理想的机会去做
of you know validation right I'm gonna
你们当中的人知道验证权，我要
validate that the bar can't be null
验证栏不能为空
right if it is an old and will have
正确的，如果它是旧的，将有
trouble so let's go ahead and now define
麻烦，让我们继续，现在定义
a beam of this type of this type of foo
这种类型的foo
or kind of beam provider method here
或这里的光束提供器方法
we'll say beam foo return a new foo and
我们会说Beam foo返回一个新的foo，
obviously this is gonna throw an
显然，这会抛出
exception because it doesn't have a a
例外，因为它没有aa
bar yet so we have to instant ate the
酒吧，所以我们必须立即吃
the the food with a bar in order for
带酒吧的食物
this to work but let's prove that our
这个工作，但让我们证明
after properties method is being called
在调用properties方法之后
this have two properties method is also
这个有两个属性的方法也是
a great place to do any kind of complex
做任何复杂事情的好地方
state setup and so on right it's a
状态设置等等，这是一个
natural place to do that
自然的地方
you
您
so there we go bar can't be no which is
所以我们去吧，不能没有，这是
what we expected right we can also
我们所期望的正确，我们也可以
imagine wanting to do this we can also
想像一下，我们也可以
imagine wanting to handle destruction
想像要处理破坏
logic right here we're creating we have
逻辑在这里，我们正在创建我们有
a nice secondary constructor if you will
一个不错的二级构造函数
to do with this kind of stuff in the
与这类东西有关
after properties method perhaps we want
经过属性方法也许我们想要
to do construction maybe want to
做建筑也许想
explicitly know out this field to
明确知道该字段以
trigger to the garbage collector that it
触发垃圾收集器
can be garbage collected right maybe
可以被垃圾收集了吧
this is a dependent or scoped being for
这是一个依赖或范围
example so in this case I can also
例如，在这种情况下，我也可以
implement disposable beam right so
实施正确的一次性光束
disposable beam is a callback that's
一次性光束是一个回调
also it's it's the mirror image if you
这也是如果你是镜像
all of initializing beam and so here
所有初始化光束等等
we're gonna say this start you know this
我们要说这开始，你知道这个
start bar equals no all right
起始栏等于“否”
remember Java unlike C++ doesn't have an
记住Java不像C ++没有
explicit notion of final answers but
最终答案的明确概念，但
dereferencing a variable can help give
取消引用变量可以帮助
the garbage collector an idea of the
垃圾收集器的想法
freedom over the the the latitude it has
拥有的自由度
to garbage collect objects so this is
垃圾收集对象，所以这是
very very convenient now this is very
非常非常方便，现在这非常
invasive right in this instance my plain
在这种情况下，侵害权是我的平原
old object my service for a hat perhaps
老物件也许是我的帽子服务
or whatever is aware of spring and
或任何知道春天和
that's not such a big deal I mean you're
没什么大不了的，我是说你
gonna be aware of spring anyway but one
无论如何都会意识到春天
could argue that lifecycle callbacks
可能会争论生命周期回调
methods in particular should should live
方法应特别有效
or work regardless of the container so
或不论容器如何工作
and that's true of course right there's
那当然是对的
no reason you couldn't for example
没有理由你不能例如
remove those interfaces especially using
删除那些接口，尤其是使用
java config right if you have XML
Java配置权，如果你有XML
there's no reason you couldn't just say
没有理由你不能只说
you know it like this you couldn't just
你知道这样，你不能只是
call the after property set method foo
调用after属性设置方法foo
dot after property set and so on and
属性设置后加点等等
everything will be okay there as well
那里一切都会好起来的
but that requires the consumer of the
但这需要
code to call that method so I suppose
代码来调用该方法，所以我想
the the real argument here the real the
真正的论点在这里真正的
best way to do is just use
最好的方法就是使用
object-oriented best practices and pass
面向对象的最佳实践和通过
them in as constructor arguments however
它们作为构造函数参数
you may want to have secondary
你可能想中学
construction logic like this and you
这样的构造逻辑和你
want to have it automatically invoked
想要自动调用它
when using a container that understands
当使用能够理解的容器时
them so for this we can use J's hard 250
他们，因此我们可以使用J的hard 250
J's or 250 is a very old standard it
J或250是一个很老的标准
came out in Java EE 5 and it describes
在Java EE 5中问世，它描述了
basic lifecycle
基本生命周期
so here I can use at pre destroy and
所以在这里我可以在销毁前使用
here I can use at sorry rather at post
在这里我可以用抱歉代替张贴
construct and at pre destroy right so
构造并在销毁前就这样
here pre destroy now if everything goes
如果一切顺利，现在就在这里摧毁
to plan we should see the same
计划我们应该看到相同的
initialization error
初始化错误
I think the validation logic should be
我认为验证逻辑应该是
in place
到位
so there we go we can see that the the
这样我们就可以看到
same effect is in place right in this
同样的效果就在这里
brother when the name is completely
哥哥，当名字完全
arbitrary after a right or you know set
权利后随心所欲或您知道设定
up whatever you want to call it right it
随便你叫什么
doesn't doesn't matter right the the
没关系没关系吧
name of the method is completely
方法的名称是完全
arbitrary now this gives us some control
现在任意，这给了我们一些控制
over the lifecycle the object naturally
在整个生命周期中，对象自然
we may have a more complex object than
我们可能有比
just a single feel that may or may not
只是一种可能会或可能不会的感觉
be no maybe we have maybe we're trying
不，也许我们有，也许我们正在尝试
to create an object that is long-running
创建一个长时间运行的对象
maybe you're managing something very
也许你在管理一些事情
very stateful and heavy and you want to
非常有状态且沉重，您想
you want to be able to start and stop
您想要能够启动和停止
and destroy and garbage collect and
销毁并收集垃圾
manage these heavy resources based on
根据这些资源来管理这些大量资源
the lifecycle the application container
应用程序容器的生命周期
this is very common for example in
这是很常见的，例如
spring innovation where we have a lot of
春季创新，我们有很多
different adapters that can be used to
可以用于不同的适配器
work with the outside world these
这些与外界合作
adapters spin up they they start
适配器旋转它们开始
monitoring an external event source for
监视外部事件源以了解
some sort of change and then based on
某种变化，然后根据
the event source they publish
他们发布的事件源
information into the application context
信息进入应用程序上下文
for downstream components to use spring
供下游组件使用弹簧
negation is very stateful right these
否定这些是非常有状态的
adapters are stateful when I'm receiving
接收时适配器是有状态的
messages from message queue I take the
来自消息队列的消息
messages elf the queue I process them I
消息精灵在队列中处理
send them downstream etc etc etc so in
将它们发送到下游等，等等
this case we need a little bit more than
在这种情况下，我们需要的不仅仅是
just a you know object initialization
只是您知道对象初始化
and destruction we we need to think
和破坏，我们需要思考
about how to manage a service and so the
关于如何管理服务等
first you know the class in this case is
首先，您知道这种情况下的课程是
the the hoist or the hook that creates
产生的葫芦或吊钩
that service so we're going to create an
该服务，因此我们将创建一个
object that implements the smart
实现智能的对象
lifecycle callbacks methods now smart
生命周期回调方法现在很聪明
lifecycle and in this case is actually
生命周期，在这种情况下实际上是
fairly simple right so a smart lifecycle
非常简单的权利，所以是一个明智的生命周期
object is just an object that is
对象只是一个对象
actually that actually implements life
实际上实现生活
cycle I suppose we should start with
周期我想我们应该从
that one first so let's go ahead and
首先，让我们继续前进，
reduce it down to just a contract of
减少到只是一个合同
lifecycle here we are so you've got to
生命周期在这里，所以您必须
start a stop and a running method and in
开始停止并运行方法
these methods you can you can see
这些方法你可以看到
whether the app your application we can
该应用程序是否可以应用
see whether the component is running
查看组件是否正在运行
whether they could the component that
他们是否可以
whether the infrastructure that they
他们是否有基础设施
with which the component is working is
组件正在使用的组件
running and you have mint adhere to
运行，你有薄荷坚持
explicitly start and stop the the
明确启动和停止
service the the thing there the enhanced
服务那里的东西增强
version of this is called smart laser
这个版本叫做智能激光
smart my cycle
聪明的我的周期
and smart lifecycle gives you extra
智慧的生命周期为您带来额外的收益
methods here you can tell spring to
您可以在这里告诉spring的方法
automatically start this component up or
自动启动该组件或
to not you can provide a destruction
否则你可以提供破坏
callback that happens when the JVM gets
JVM获取时发生的回调
shut down when the application can shut
当应用程序可以关闭时关闭
down or whatever comes first you get a
下降或首先发生的事情
callback here for starting and stopping
在这里回调以开始和停止
but of course stopping may not happen
但当然停止可能不会发生
quick enough right so it's very useful
足够快的权利，所以它非常有用
to provide a custom runnable that can be
提供可以
run on the JVM shut down a hook and we
在JVM上运行，关闭钩子，我们
have here a status object that we can
在这里有一个状态对象，我们可以
use to determine whether the object is
用于确定对象是否为
running and we also have this order idea
运行，我们也有这个订单的想法
of a phase the order in which this
一个阶段的顺序
application should be executed right so
申请应该正确执行
that that is very very useful in
那是非常非常有用的
particular so they eased objects are
特别是这样他们放宽对象
useful if you have something great
如果您有很棒的东西很有用
stateful perhaps one is dependent upon
有状态的，也许一个人依赖
something else right so we have here the
其他正确的东西，所以我们在这里
interface and we can see there are
界面，我们可以看到有
different well-known phases sorry you
不同的知名阶段对不起你
can see that the the the phase is just a
可以看到阶段只是一个
number right the number but it fall to
数字正确的数字，但它落入
zero and that just means it has no no
零，那就意味着它没有
particular import right no particular
特殊进口权无特殊要求
importance but it's up to you to provide
重要性，但要由您提供
that phase if you want for ordering
如果您想订购该阶段
purposes right so it gets used here in
正确的目的，所以它在这里使用
the lifecycle processor or the default
生命周期处理器或默认处理器
like it my cycle processor that a spring
喜欢我的弹簧循环处理器
uses to to you know to honor the
用于告知您荣誉
presence of the lifecycle interface in
存在生命周期接口
encode it ends up creating objects and
编码它最终创建对象并
ends up putting objects that have the
最终将具有
same phase in the same life cycle group
同一生命周期组中的同一阶段
so in this way you have a sort of a way
因此，您可以通过某种方式
of saying this is gonna happen before
说这会在之前发生
that etc okay this is for long-lived
等等，好吧，这是长寿的
component this is again I think it by
组件这再次是我认为
the time you need this you're very much
当你需要这个的时候，你非常
in the realm of writing a component that
在编写组件的领域
is explicitly leaning on the lifecycle
明确依赖生命周期
capabilities of the spring frame of
弹簧框架的功能
container not just instant inning plane
集装箱不仅是即时的飞机
objects sometimes you have complex
对象有时候你很复杂
objects that
那些
more or maybe of objects that that you
更多或者也许是您
don't instance it directly maybe you
不要直接实例化，也许你
have objects that live somewhere else or
有物体住在其他地方
they are external to the application
它们在应用程序外部
context and and so you wanna provide a
上下文，因此您想提供一个
definition for that object a case in
该对象的定义
point of course is the anything you look
当然，你要看的东西
up from Jane di now Jane di is and is a
从简迪开始，现在简迪现在是
directory it's a Java native you know it
目录是您知道的Java本机目录
stands for Java naming and directory
代表Java命名和目录
interface it's a it's a way of looking
界面，这是一种看待方式
up keys and values in a in a context
在上下文中上调键和值
which is common in a lot of application
在很多应用中很常见
servers so this is a very kind of old
服务器，所以这是一种很旧的
idea but it's still very germane to what
想法，但与什么仍然有密切关系
we're trying to do here in the case of
我们正在尝试在这种情况下
Jane di spring doesn't instantiate the
Jane Di Spring没有实例化
objects instead it manages an object in
对象，而是管理对象
the context by looking up the object in
通过查找对象来确定上下文
some other thing and some other memory
一些其他的事情和一些其他的记忆
in the JVM somewhere right so in the
在JVM中正确的位置
case of the application server its
应用服务器的情况
memory being managed by the application
由应用程序管理的内存
server co-located with your application
服务器与您的应用程序位于同一位置
so we want to be able to dereference
所以我们希望能够取消引用
that object to look it up and to make it
那个对象来查找并制作它
available to our code so maybe want to
可用于我们的代码，所以也许想
look up a data source the application
查找数据源应用程序
server will manage the data source
服务器将管理数据源
that'll manage the connection pool it
它会管理连接池
will provide all that for us and we want
将为我们提供一切，我们想要
to use that in our spring managed codes
在我们的春季托管代码中使用它
who want to inject the data source here
谁想要在这里注入数据源
we can use a factory beam right so we
我们可以使用工厂光束，所以我们
could actually create a Jane di factory
实际上可以创建一个简迪工厂
beam right in the object factory mean
光束在物体工厂中的均值
Janie Hydrick tractor beam like this and
Janie Hydrick拖拉机横梁像这样和
the Jane di fetch factory beam it has a
简迪（Jane di fetch）工厂光束
lot of parameters that we could provide
我们可以提供的很多参数
right so set the you know set the the
对，所以设置您知道的设置
Jane di name the Jane a 10 but if you
简·迪（Jane di）将简命名为10，但如果您
want the resource Ref they expected type
想要资源Ref他们期望的类型
if you want you know we were a lot of
如果您想知道我们很多
different things that we could provide
我们可以提供的不同的东西
here including it property values that
这里包括它的属性值
we can use to do reference to Jane di
我们可以用来参考简迪
environment you know to resolve the
您知道要解决的环境
actual environment in the first place
首先是实际环境
all this stuff is expected to be
所有这些东西都有望成为
provided but then finally once all
提供，但最后一次全部
that's done spring once we return that
一旦我们返回，那是春天
we return FB right spring will take all
我们返回FB右弹簧将占据所有
those variables into account the factory
这些变量考虑到工厂
will take all those variables into
将所有这些变量纳入
account and then use them in the get
帐户，然后在获取中使用它们
object method here so get object which
这里的对象方法，所以获取对象
returns this Jane di object which of
返回此Jane di对象中的哪个
course is the object that was
当然是那个对象
looked up for you after the after
在之后寻找你
properties method was said so he was
有人说属性方法，所以他
saying Janie Hydrick tickles Jane the
说珍妮·海德里克挠着简的
object part Partridge factory kinda
对象部分ridge工厂有点
great Jane the object part C etc etc etc
伟大的简对象部分C等等等
right and so otherwise we're looking it
对，所以否则我们正在寻找它
up so the the the construction of the
因此，
object is very complex but we don't care
对象很复杂，但我们不在乎
because all we need to know is that
因为我们需要知道的是
we're gonna have a data source of the
我们将有一个数据源
right type that'll be managed for us
正确的类型将为我们管理
right so we can in sprint when spring
好的，所以我们可以在春天时冲刺
runs this it's not going to actually
运行它实际上并不会
manage this factory beam in fact instead
实际上管理这个工厂光束
it's going to manage the product of the
它要管理的产品
factory main in this case the product of
在这种情况下，工厂主要是
the factory beam will be the object that
工厂光束将成为
gets returned by by calling into the
通过调用返回
Jandy a context like this but look up
詹迪这样的背景，但要抬头
what's a dandy a fall back fall back we
什么是花花公子一个回退回退我们
got a an object that gets returned and
有一个被返回的对象，
the the type of the object in this case
在这种情况下对象的类型
is just have a lying an object but
只是撒谎而已
spring likes to know you know it likes
春天喜欢知道你知道喜欢
to know what the type can be cast to if
知道如果可以转换为什么类型
necessary so for example it provides a
必要的，例如，它提供了
callback interface here a contract in
回调接口在这里合同
the factory being method a rather
工厂是一种方法
interface called get object type in here
此处称为获取对象类型的接口
you're supposed to return the type of
你应该返回的类型
the object that's being returned so that
返回的对象，以便
spring can do validation you know before
春天可以做你之前知道的验证
the application starts up it wants to
应用程序启动它想要
validate that there are objects of a
验证是否存在一个对象
certain type in the context maybe it
上下文中的某种类型
sees a reference for a data source in
看到有关数据源的参考
some component code that needs to be
一些组件代码需要
injected it doesn't know where to get it
注射它不知道从哪里得到
yet it just wants to prove or just wants
但是它只是想证明还是想要
to know if there's anything in the
知道里面有什么
context that will eventually result in a
最终会导致
beam of that type and the fact you being
这种类型的光束和事实
well results in there in that end being
最终结果是
of that type so by having that callback
这种类型的，因此通过回调
method we can avoid forcing spring to
方法，我们可以避免强迫弹簧
you know instantiate aggressively and
你知道积极实例化和
early that the datasource before it's
早于数据源
needed so let's take a very simple
需要，所以让我们做一个非常简单的
example let's say that we want to create
例如，假设我们要创建
a public static class foo and we'll take
一个公共的静态类foo，我们将采取
a whoops will create a public static
会创建一个公共静态变量
class foo factory
foo类工厂
bean implementing factory being of type
Bean实现工厂类型
foo and we'll create our own very very
foo，我们将创建自己的非常非常
simple foo ok so again the idea here is
简单的foo好，所以这里的想法是
to have complex initialization to hide
有复杂的初始化要隐藏
that logic maybe I have maybe foo is
逻辑，也许我有，也许foo是
actually an interface right in this case
在这种情况下实际上是一个接口
we have public static class foo one
我们有公共静态类foo一
public static class food - and of course
公共静态食品-当然
this doesn't need to be a static and
这不必是静态的，
maybe in my in the case of my factory
也许以我为例
bean I want to have a boolean that says
bean 我想有一个布尔值说
prefer one right so I'll say that that's
更喜欢一项权利，所以我会说那是
gonna be true by default and but it
默认情况下会是真的，但是
could be something else
可能是别的东西
okay the setter there we are and we know
好吧，我们那里的塞特犬，我们知道
that the object no matter what the type
那个物体不管什么类型
is gonna be of type foo so we can tell
将会是foo类型，所以我们可以知道
spring about that oh sorry we can tell
关于那个春天，哦，抱歉，我们可以告诉
spring about that here and the object
关于这里和对象的春天
type method we know it's gonna be we
类型方法，我们知道它将是我们
know that it could be a dependently
知道这可能是一个依赖
scope thing we could have more than one
我们可以拥有多个范围的东西
in the application context so I just
在应用程序上下文中，所以我只是
like to leave this false by default but
喜欢默认保留为false，但是
I suppose there's no reason if you're
我想你没有理由
absolutely sure that there's are never
绝对确定永远不会
gonna be more than one that that
将不止一个
couldn't be true that said that is
说那是不对的
merely a suggestion there are some of
只是一个建议，有一些
these cases where spring will override
这些情况下，弹簧将超越
that behavior that value so keep that in
那种有价值的行为，所以要坚持下去
mind now let's create the fool here
现在，让我们在这里创建傻瓜
we're gonna say return this type prefer
我们会说返回这种类型更喜欢
foo one or prefer one if that's true
foo一个或更喜欢一个（如果是这样）
new foo one otherwise new fool - okay so
新foo一个否则是新傻瓜-好的
we're creating a a different object
我们正在创建一个不同的对象
based on configuration so this is not
基于配置，所以这不是
the same as as a varying the
与变体相同
construction of the object in the
对象中的构造
construction itself now you could
现在可以自己建造
actually just stick an add component on
实际上只是在上面添加了一个组件
this but remember you're gonna use this
这个，但是记住你会用这个
fact to be in some more than once right
事实不止一次
so I would say at being full factory
所以我会说在正式工厂
bean foo return new foo factory bean
bean foo返回新的foo工厂bean
there we are and the food that I'll get
我们在那里，我会得到的食物
by default in this case is the the first
默认情况下，这是第一个
one right the food one I could change
一对食物我可以改变
that right so again what I'm doing is
没错，所以我要做的是
I'm creating a factory bean spring
我正在创建一个工厂 bean 弹簧
doesn't care about this object here it
不在乎这个对象
doesn't know about the factory it sees
不知道看到的工厂
the product of the factory being this
工厂的商品是这个
one here this is very common especially
这在这里很常见
before where he had complex
在他复杂的地方之前
initialization and the only way to
初始化和唯一的方法
create these objects in spring was to
在春天创建这些对象是为了
use XML now of course we have Java
现在使用XML当然我们有Java
configuration so these Java
配置这些Java
configuration methods are very very
配置方法非常非常
versatile you can do anything in Java
多功能，您可以用Java做任何事情
they want here too
他们也想在这里
arrived at the objects so there's no
到达了物体，所以没有
really there's a reason no really real
真的有一个没有真正真实的理由
reason to have this extra adapter I mean
我有这个额外适配器的原因
it's a nice plate it's a nice idea it's
这是一个很好的盘子，这是一个好主意
a nice place to sort of codify
编纂的好地方
construction right construction is a
建设权建设是一个
very interesting thing to do so this is
这样做很有趣，这是
an implementation of the factory pattern
工厂模式的实现
but it is very much a thing that I
但这是我非常重要的一件事
wouldn't recommend particularly for new
不会特别推荐新的
code if you're using Java configuration
代码，如果您使用的是Java配置
you can get away with creating the
您可以摆脱创建
objects in in the Java config method
Java config方法中的对象
itself or use a builder or a custom
本身或使用构建器或自定义
object right you don't we have custom
对象的权利，你不是我们有自定义
objects that do a lot of the hard work
做很多艰苦工作的对象
for you so you can say return new jndi
为您服务，所以您可以说返回新的jndi
data source lookup india ID data so no
数据源查找印度ID数据，所以没有
locator delegate lookup and then pass in
定位器委托查找，然后传递
the the Jan di string right so you get a
Jan di字符串正确，所以您得到一个
lot of functionality out of the box you
开箱即用的很多功能
don't really need the factory Beam
真的不需要工厂Beam
anymore but if you see it it's it's very
了，但是如果你看到它的话
useful to understand what it's doing
了解它在做什么很有用
right and to understand how to work with
正确并了解如何使用
it there are a lot of fact to beans in
里面有很多事实
spring as you can imagine in my mirror
你在我的镜子里可以想象得到的春天
class path with just a few spring jars
带有几个春季罐子的课堂路径
on the class path I've got all these
在上课的路上，我已经拥有了所有这些
different factory beans that allow me to
不同的工厂 bean 让我
create caches and date/time for matters
创建事务的缓存和日期/时间
and JMX infrastructure and services and
以及JMX基础架构和服务以及
thread pools and tasks executors and
线程池和任务执行程序以及
Yambol factories and all these different
Yambol工厂和所有这些不同
things right these are all just what
对的事情这些都是
I've got in the class mats and they've
我有课垫，他们有
been around forever this last section
永远都在这最后一节
let's take a look at the the new nicety
让我们来看看新事物
a nice tool inside of a spring framework
Spring Framework 中的一个不错的工具
4.3 which if you're using the spring
4.3如果您正在使用弹簧
boot 1.4 it's already included Spring
引导1.4，它已经包含Spring
Framework 4.3 it's fairly new having
框架4.3相当新
just come out earlier this year and it
刚在今年早些时候问世
includes a nice feature called injection
包含一个不错的功能，称为注入
point which is very much inspired by the
这点非常受启发
class of the same name in CDI okay so
CDI中具有相同名称的类，这样
the injection point is very very useful
注射点非常有用
if you want to make your code aware of
如果您想让代码知道
the object into which is being injected
被注入的对象
and it's pretty hard for me to think of
我很难想到
any other example besides the one that's
除了那个以外的任何其他例子
kind of bandied around pretty obviously
很明显地
pretty commonly which is that of a
很常见的是
logger so we're gonna go ahead and
记录器，所以我们要继续
create a logger we're gonna say I want
创建一个记录器，我们要说我想要
to create a logger I'm gonna use the
创建一个记录器，我将使用
injection point type here to create a
在此处创建注入点类型
logger that is aware of the other class
知道其他类的记录器
int which is being
int正在
inject it so I'll say injection point
注入它，所以我会说注入点
get declaring element or get to coloring
声明元素或着色
type get name I rather get member that
输入获取名称，我宁愿获取成员
gig
演出
declaring class get name okay so I've
声明班级名称可以，所以我已经
got a lager them providing and now I can
他们提供了更大的啤酒，现在我可以
create a component that needs it but of
创建一个需要它的组件
course I'm gonna have multiple
当然我要有多个
components right I'll have multiple
组件正确，我将拥有多个
components that each have their own
每个都有自己的组件
lager right that's the whole point I
对了，这就是我的重点
want have a log or that that has for its
想要一个日志或具有它的
value here at the class in which it's in
在这里所在的班级上重视
which exist otherwise I would have you
存在否则我会拥有你
know otherwise I could just do the old
知道否则我可以做旧的
way so logging component if I did the
这样的方式记录组件，如果我做了
old way I'd have something like
旧的方式我会喜欢
logger.log or lager get lager right and
logger.log或lager正确获得更大的啤酒，并且
I just say get class and that would work
我只是说上课就行了
certainly but it's it it ends up getting
当然，但是它最终变得越来越
tedious right so in this case I'm gonna
乏味的权利，所以在这种情况下，我要
just inject the lager and now I've got
只是注入啤酒，现在我有
it centrally managed I can actually
它可以集中管理，我实际上可以
change the configuration once and it
一次更改配置
affects all so configured lagers but
影响所有如此配置的标签，但
because I may have multiple components
因为我可能有多个组成部分
each with their own class I don't want a
每个人都有自己的班级，我不想
singleton right this won't work I want
单身人士，这是行不通的，我想要
to make this scoped to a prototype so
使它成为原型
I'll do that I'll turn this into a
我会做的，我会把它变成一个
prototype you may use it for other
原型，您可以将其用于其他
scopes as well you may say oh I want to
范围也可以说哦，我想
have a session sculpt or whatever but
进行会话雕刻或其他操作
the point is its prototype is fine it's
关键是它的原型很好
a cheap enough object it doesn't any
足够便宜的东西
matter so I've got now an object that's
很重要，所以我现在有了一个
gonna be injected and again I could make
将被注射，我可以再次
this add on a wire but remember another
这增加了电线，但要记住另一个
nice sitting in 4.3 is that I don't need
4.3的好感觉是我不需要
to okay so let's just use a lager hello
好的，所以我们只使用一个更大的问候
world old and now we can start that up
世界悠久，现在我们可以开始了
and we should see the logger logging as
我们应该看到记录器记录为
though it had been defined inside of a
尽管它已在
login component which of course is in
登录组件，这当然在
turn defined inside of the spring aware
定义弹簧内部的转弯
application and there we are there's our
应用程序，我们在那里
hello world okay so that's a very cool
你好，世界很好，这很酷
feature I think I think it's very useful
功能我认为我认为这非常有用
you'll find a lot of use for that
您会发现很多用途
hopefully in your code it's certainly
希望在您的代码中肯定是
it's not the only way to get a longer
这不是延长寿命的唯一方法
when I talked about this on Twitter and
当我在Twitter上谈论这一点时，
at Starbucks man a few people responded
在星巴克，有几个人回应
with mentions of the goofy at log
在日志中提到高飞
annotation which is the groovy language
注释，这是时髦的语言
itself has a length annotation to do
本身有一个长度注释
that and Lombok
那和龙目岛
presumably borrowing or at least being
大概是借用或至少是
inspired by what you can do in goo V
受Goo V的启发
also has an SL at 4 J annotation both of
在4 J注释处也有一个SL
which using user code sort of compile
使用用户代码进行哪种编译
time or run basic initialization time
时间或运行基本初始化时间
magic 2 to insert or inject a logger
插入或插入记录器的magic 2
that you can use with a well known
可以与知名的
variable type and that's all well and
变量类型，一切都很好，
good I just think this is a little bit
好，我只是觉得这有点
this is nice if you're using spring
如果您使用弹簧，这很好
you've you want to remove those public
您是否要删除这些公开的
static final loggers from all of your
所有您的静态最终记录器
code
码
all right well with that thank you very
很好，非常感谢
much I hope you enjoyed I'll see you end
我非常希望你喜欢我会看到你结束
you
您